<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Let's Review</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Let's Review</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 21:45:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://letsreview.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discord Server</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/posts/discord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 21:45:29 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/posts/discord/</guid><description>We have set up a Discord server for our collaboration efforts. You can use it as a foundation for your review group or to simply get in touch with us.
Just use the discord link on our main page.
See you there!</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 18:13:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/resources/</guid><description> Forming a new Group Roles in Code Review Groups Scaling Code Review Groups Presentations 2022
Kielux, Code Review - Wer suchet, der findet 2021
rC3, Lets review code together - einfach mal machen</description></item><item><title>Forming a Group</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/forming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 18:12:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/forming/</guid><description>So you want to form a group but are unsure which format fits best or which obstacles might lie in front of you? Then let&amp;rsquo;s review some possible concepts and how they differ.
It is best to imagine the kind of group you want to be part of. Subtle differences at core aspects could otherwise disappoint you or others.
The following core aspects should be considered.
Visibility Do you want to have a safe space?</description></item><item><title>Roles in Code Review Groups</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 18:12:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/roles/</guid><description>Just like in any given group of people, diversity in personalities has positive impacts on the overall group performance. But what kind of roles or archetypes exist from a review perspective?
Hacker A hacker tries to disassemble and tinker with any given aspect of a product in order to understand every single bit of it. Applying a good amount of creativity by thinking out of the box might reveal rare edge cases and other often overlooked or even novel bugs or lack of design.</description></item><item><title>Scaling Code Review Groups</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/scaling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 18:12:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/scaling/</guid><description>Our idea of code review groups is that people actively work together. This implies that everyone contributes by leading a review or adding feedback.
Vertical Scaling If a group scales vertically, then more and more members join. Huge groups cannot operate as flexible as small ones and it becomes more and more difficult to integrate everyone into active roles.
Eventually not everyone can actively contribute anymore. You can try to compensate this by splitting members into active contributors to a session and a more passive audience.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 23:17:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/about/</guid><description>Statements Mission We offer a platform for people who want to improve their code review skills together.
Vision People are able to select and improve the best matching software for their requirements.</description></item><item><title>Groups</title><link>https://letsreview.github.io/groups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 23:17:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://letsreview.github.io/groups/</guid><description> CasualCCodeReviewers (GitHub), reviewing C code LetsReadJava (GitHub), reviewing Java code ThanatosisSerpentis (GitHub), reviewing Python code</description></item></channel></rss>